Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Original Accession, 1906-1988
  - Correspondence I, 1923-1988
    - Fundacion Joaquin Costa (Pedro Schwartz), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - Fürth, J. Herbert, 1952-1984 (Box-folder 21: 8)
    - Fuster, J. M., 1976 (Box-folder 21: 9)
    - Gadamer, Hans-Georg, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 21: 10)
    - Gadol, Eugene T., 1978 (Box-folder 21: 11)
    - Gallois, Marian, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21: 12)
    - Garlund, Torsten, 1967 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    - Garrett, Andrew, 1980 (Box-folder 21: 14)
    - Gates, Jeffrey R., 1983 (Box-folder 21: 15)
    - Gearing, H., 1938 (Box-folder 21: 16)
    - Gehlen, Arnold, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 21: 17)
    - Gellner, Ernest, 1978 (Box-folder 21: 18)
    - Gemeinsame Forschungsstelle (Roland Lindner), 1982 (Box-folder 21: 19)
    - Gemper, Bodo B., 1968-1976 (Box-folder 21: 20)
    - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade [See Tumlir, Jan]
    - General Electric Corporation, 1956 (Box-folder 21: 21)
    - Georg-August-Universität (A. Scheibe, Bruno Seidel, Th. Suranyi-Unger), 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21: 22)
    - George Mason University (James M. Buchanan, Karen I. Vaughn), 1983-1985 (Box-folder 21: 23)
    - George, Michael, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 21: 24)
    - Gerbino, Kenneth J., 1982 (Box-folder 21: 25)
    - Germany. Botschaft (Japan), 1978 (Box-folder 21: 26)
    - Gesellschaft für die Verleihung des Internationalen Karlspreises der Stadt Aachen (Herr Malangre, Herr Willms), re Otto Habsburg, 1986 (Box-folder 21: 27)
    - Gesellschaft für Wirtschafts- und Sozialwissenschaften, 1963-1986 (Box-folder 21: 28)
    - Gewirth, Alan, 1963 (Box-folder 21: 29)
    - Gibson, James J. and Eleanor J., 1954 (Box-folder 21: 30)
    - Giersch, Herbert, 1963-1977 (Box-folder 21: 31)
    - Gilbert, Martin, 1984 (Box-folder 21: 32)
    - Giscard d'Estaing, Valery, 1975 (Box-folder 21: 33)
    - Gissurarson, Hannes H., 1982-1985 (Box-folder 21: 34)
    - Giuliani, Alessandro, 1977 (Box-folder 21: 35)
    - Gladstone Club (Roger Pincham), 1977 (Box-folder 21: 36)
    - Gladwyn, Lord, 1977 (Box-folder 21: 37)
    - Glasner, David, 1970-1985 (Box-folder 21: 38)
    - Global Economic Action Institute, 1985 (Box-folder 21: 39)
    - Gocht, Rolf, 1965-1979 (Box-folder 21: 40)
    - Godart van der Kroon, A. M. Th., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 21: 41)
    - Godschalk, H., 1985 (Box-folder 21: 42)
    - Gold Standard Corporation (Conrad J. Braun), 1977-1987 (Box-folder 21: 43)
    - Goldberger, Edmund, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 22: 1)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1964 (Box-folder 22: 2)
    - Gombrich, Ernst H., 1966-1979 (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - Gomulka, Stanislaw, 1978 (Box-folder 22: 4)
    - Goodell, Grace E., 1980 (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - Goodrich, Pierre F., 1958-1968 (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - Gordon Walker, Patrick, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - Gorski, Bohdan J., 1968-1982 (Box-folder 22: 8)
    - Gottinger, Hans W., 1977-1982 (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - Gotz, Alexander, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 10)
    - Gould, Stephen Jay, 1981 (Box-folder 22: 11)
    - Graham, Malise Lynedoch, 1981 (Box-folder 22: 12)
    - Grathoff, Richard, 1978 (Box-folder 22: 13)
    - Gray, John N., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 22: 14)
    - Great Britain. Consulate (Innsbruck), 1971-1976 (Box-folder 22: 15)
    - Great Britain. Consulate (Stuttgart), 1962-1977 (Box-folder 22: 16)
    - Great Britain. Embassy (Sweden), 1974 (Box-folder 22: 17)
    - Greaves, Percy L., Jr., 1976 (Box-folder 22: 18)
    - Grede, William J., 1971-1976 (Box-folder 22: 19)
    - Greenfield, Harry I., 1976 (Box-folder 22: 20)
    - Gregersen, Magnus I., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22: 21)
    - Gregory, Theodore E. G., 1955-1961 (Box-folder 22: 22)
    - Greiffenhagen, Martin, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 23)
    - Griffin, Thomas, 1984 (Box-folder 22: 24)
    - Groeben, Hans von der, 1969 (Box-folder 22: 25)
    - Groenewegen, P. D., 1973 (Box-folder 22: 26)
    - Groseclose, Tim, 1970 (Box-folder 22: 27)
    - Grüber, Guenther R., 1964 (Box-folder 22: 28)
    - Grüber, U., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 22: 29)
    - Gruenwald, Oskar, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 22: 30)
    - Guan, Doemou, 1966 (Box-folder 22: 31)
    - Gudin, Eugenio, 1957 (Box-folder 22: 32)
    - Guillebaud, C. W., 1959 (Box-folder 22: 33)
    - Guillet de Monthoux, Pierre, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 34)
    - Gunther, Eduard W., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 22: 35)
    - Gunther, Eva, 1982 (Box-folder 22: 36)
    - Gustavus Adolphus College, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 22: 37)
    - Gutmann, G., 1970-1975 (Box-folder 22: 38)
    - Gutowski, Armin, 1965-1985 (Box-folder 22: 39)
      Includes correspondence with Ulrich Leffson and Erich Welter.
    - Gwartney, James D., 1979 (Box-folder 22: 40)
    - Haag, John J., re Othmar Spann, 1967 (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - Haakonssen, Knud, 1974 (Box-folder 23: 2)
    - Haberle, Peter, 1964 (Box-folder 23: 3)
    - Haberler, Gottfried, undated (Box-folder 23: 4)
    - Habsburg, Otto, 1958-1984 (Box-folder 23: 5)
      Includes correspondence with Ernst Thun.
    - Hacking, Ian, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 23: 6)
    - Hagama, Shinjiro, undated (Box-folder 23: 7)
    - Hagedorn, Tom, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 23: 8)
    - Hahn, Oswald, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 23: 9)
    - Haken, H., 1984 (Box-folder 23: 10)
    - Haley, Evetts, Jr., 1977 (Box-folder 23: 11)
    - Haller, Rudolf, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 23: 12)
    - Hamburger, Joseph and Lotte, 1955-1985 (Box-folder 23: 13)
    - Hammerle, Max Wilhelm, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 23: 14)
    - Hammett, William M. H., 1983-1986 (Box-folder 23: 15)
      Includes reviews of Charles Murray, Losing Ground.
    - Hamowy, Ronald, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 23: 16)
    - Hanke, Maurizio, 1984 (Box-folder 23: 17)
    - Hanke, Steve H., 1982-1984 (Box-folder 23: 18)
    - Hankook Ilbo [See Korea Times]
    - Hanns Martin Schleyer-Stiftung (F. Hilterhaus), 1985-1987 (Box-folder 23: 19)
    - Hansen, Reginald, including re Carl Menger, 1967 (Box-folder 23: 20)
    - Harcourt, G. C., 1976 (Box-folder 23: 21)
    - Hardin, Garrett, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 23: 22)
    - Hardy, Alister, 1979 (Box-folder 23: 23)
    - Hare, Richard M., 1965 (Box-folder 23: 24)
    - Harris, J. W., 1972 (Box-folder 23: 25)
    - Harris, Ralph, 1981 (Box-folder 23: 26)
    - Harris, Roy, 1984 (Box-folder 23: 27)
    - Harry G. Johnson Memorial Fund, 1977 (Box-folder 23: 28)
    - Hart, David, 1980 (Box-folder 23: 29)
    - Hartshorne, Charles, 1960 (Box-folder 23: 30)
    - Hartwell, R. Max, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 23: 31)
    - Hartwell, Robert M., 1963 (Box-folder 23: 32)
    - Harvard University, 1952 (Box-folder 23: 33)
    - Hasegawa, Takehiko, 1981 (Box-folder 23: 34)
    - Hauptverband der Österreichischen Sparkassen, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 23: 35)
    - Havender, William R., 1975-1980 (Box-folder 23: 36)
    - Havrilesky, Thomas M., 1984 (Box-folder 23: 37)
    - Hawtrey, R. G., 1942-1952 (Box-folder 23: 38)
    - Haynes, Michael, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 23: 39)
    - Hebb, D. O., 1952 (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - Heertje, A., 1982 (Box-folder 24: 2)
    - Hegemann, Franz Josef, 1982 (Box-folder 24: 3)
    - Heidrich, Holger, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 24: 4)
    - Heilperin, Michael A., 1963 (Box-folder 24: 5)
    - Heinrich, H. G., 1984 (Box-folder 24: 6)
    - Heinz, 1962 (Box-folder 24: 7)
    - Heismann, Gunter, 1984 (Box-folder 24: 8)
    - Hejl, Lubos J., 1975 (Box-folder 24: 9)
    - Hellenic Society for Humanistic Studies (Professor Skiades, Chryssoula Soile), 1981 (Box-folder 24: 10)
    - Heller, Peter, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 24: 11)
    - Hellmann, Winfried, 1979 (Box-folder 24: 12)
    - Helmi, Oesman J., 1967 (Box-folder 24: 13)
    - Hempel, Carl G., 1952 (Box-folder 24: 14)
    - Henderson, David R., 1978 (Box-folder 24: 15)
    - Hennessy, Jossleyn, 1965 (Box-folder 24: 16)
    - Hennings, K. H., 1969-1985 (Box-folder 24: 17)
    - Hennis, Wilhelm, 1967 (Box-folder 24: 18)
    - Henry Regnery Company, 1951-1984 (Box-folder 24: 19)
    - Henry Salvatori Center [See Claremont Men's College]
    - Hensel, Paul K., re Gustav Boehmer, 1966 (Box-folder 24: 20)
    - Herder-Dorneich, Philipp, 1968 (Box-folder 24: 21)
    - Heritage Foundation (Arthur L. Conrad, Edwin J. Feulner, Jr., Richard B. McKenzie), 1955, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 24: 22)
      Includes two organizations of the name Heritage Foundation, one of Chicago from 1955 and the other from Washington D.C., 1978-1985, including correspondence with John K. Andrews, Jr. and Julian L. Simon.
    - Heritage Trust (John M. Calabrini), 1985 (Box-folder 24: 23)
    - Hermann, Armin, 1976 (Box-folder 24: 24)
    - Hermann-Ehlers-Akademie (Walter Bernhardt), 1977 (Box-folder 24: 25)
    - Hermens, Ferdinand A., 1964-1987 (Box-folder 24: 26)
    - Hess, 1962 (Box-folder 24: 27)
    - Hessen, Robert, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 24: 28)
    - Hessischer Kreis (K. K. von der Groeben, Gisela Leicher, Georg Thonet), 1982 (Box-folder 24: 29)
    - Hevesy, Paul von, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 24: 30)
    - Heyne, Paul, 1975 (Box-folder 24: 31)
    - Hicks, John R., 1965-1984 (Box-folder 24: 32)
    - Hill, James F., 1978 (Box-folder 24: 33)
    - Hill, Karl O., 1964-1981 (Box-folder 24: 34)
    - Hillsdale College (George C. Roche, III, Peter C. McCarty), 1975-1985 (Box-folder 25: 1)
      Includes correspondence with John K. Andrews, Jr., Don Lipsett, Arthur A. Shenfield, George W. Trivoli, and Ronald L. Trowbridge.
    - Himmelfarb, Gertrude, 1962 (Box-folder 25: 2)
    - Hinshaw, C. Alton, 1984 (Box-folder 25: 3)
    - Hirayama, Albert L., 1982 (Box-folder 25: 4)
    - Hirshleifer, Jack, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 25: 5)
    - History and Theory, 1966 (Box-folder 25: 6)
    - History of Economics Society (Laurence S. Moss), 1985 (Box-folder 25: 7)
    - Hitotsubashi University Library, 1964-1981 (Box-folder 25: 8)
    - Hodes, Isidor, 1965 (Box-folder 25: 9)
    - Hoerster, Norbert, 1977 (Box-folder 25: 10)
    - Hof, Hans-Joachim, 1967-1977 (Box-folder 25: 11)
    - Hoff, Ole-Jacob, 1978 (Box-folder 25: 12)
    - Hoff, Trygve J. B., undated (Box-folder 25: 13)
    - Hogan, W. P., 1977 (Box-folder 25: 14)
    - Holbach Informationsdienste (Hans-Peter Holbach), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 25: 15)
    - Holland Forum (M. Stern), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 25: 16)
    - Hollerbach, H., 1969 (Box-folder 25: 17)
    - Holze, Frank B., 1964 (Box-folder 25: 18)
    - Holzer, Henry Mark, 1980 (Box-folder 25: 19)
    - Holzwarth, Fritz, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 25: 20)
      Includes correspondence with Helmut Groner.
    - Hong Kong Economic Journal (Steven N. S. Cheung), 1979 (Box-folder 25: 21)
    - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace (W. Glenn Campbell, Dennis L. Bark, Richard T. Burress, Milorad M. Drachkovitch, Thomas G. Moore, Charles G. Palm, Alvin Rabushka), 1968-1986 (Box-folder 25: 22)
      Includes correspondence with Karl Brandt, Albert Hunold, Kurt R. Leube, Willy Linder (Neue Zurcher Zeitung), Eva Ropke, and Hans Willgerodt.
    - Hoover Institution Press (David L. Fleenor, Mickey G. Hamilton, Walter Lammi), 1979-1984 (Box-folder 25: 23)
      Includes correspondence with Chiaki Nishiyama.
    - Hoppmann, Erich, 1968 (Box-folder 25: 24)
    - Horkheimer, Max, 1964 (Box-folder 25: 25)
    - Horwitz, Ralph, 1963-1980 (Box-folder 25: 26)
    - Hosono, Koichi, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 25: 27)
    - Hosta, Geoffrey M., 1982 (Box-folder 25: 28)
    - Howard, David H., 1977 (Box-folder 25: 29)
    - Howe, Geoffrey, 1975 (Box-folder 25: 30)
    - Howell, Ralph, 1974 (Box-folder 25: 31)
    - Hsia, Adrian, 1967 (Box-folder 25: 32)
    - Hsiao, Tseng, 1964-1983 (Box-folder 25: 33)
      Includes correspondence with Ralph Harris.
    - Hsu, Ta-chuan, 1965 (Box-folder 25: 34)
    - Hüber, Richard, 1976 (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - Hubner, Kurt, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 26: 2)
    - Huckel, Fritz A., 1976-1983 (Box-folder 26: 3)
    - Humanistische Union, 1964 (Box-folder 26: 4)
    - Hummel, Fritz, 1963 (Box-folder 26: 5)
    - Hummel, Jeffrey Rogers, 1977 (Box-folder 26: 6)
    - Hungerland, Heinz, 1981 (Box-folder 26: 7)
    - Hutchison, Terence W., 1981-1983 (Box-folder 26: 8)
    - Hutt, William Harold, 1953-1984 (Box-folder 26: 9)
    - Ichord, Richard H., 1976 (Box-folder 26: 10)
    - Ihara, Takashi, undated (Box-folder 26: 11)
    - Ikeda, Yoshizo, 1981 (Box-folder 26: 12)
    - Illies, J., 1979 (Box-folder 26: 13)
    - Inagawa, Teruyoshi [See Japan. Embassy (Germany)]
    - Industrial Bank of Japan (Yoshitada Uchiyama), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 26: 14)
    - Industrie- und Handelskammer Darmstadt (Juniorenkreis) [See Wirtschaftsjunioren der Industrie- und Handelskammer Darmstadt]
    - Industrie- und Handelskammer des Saarlandes (Hanspeter Georgi), 1978 (Box-folder 26: 15)
    - Industrie- und Handelskammer zu Dortmund (Wilhelm Utermann), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 26: 16)
    - Industrie- und Handelskammer zu Koblenz (Karl Darscheid, R. Hagmann, Hanno Ludwig), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 26: 17)
    - Inquiry [See Cato Institute]
    - Institut der Wirtschaftsprüfer (Lothar Schruff), 1984 (Box-folder 26: 18)
    - Institut Economique de Paris (Fred Aftalion, Francois Guillaumat, Guy Plunier), 1983-1986 (Box-folder 26: 19)
    - Institut für Asienkunde (Bernhard Grossmann), 1966 (Box-folder 26: 20)
    - Institut für das Spar-, Giro- und Kreditwesen (Werner Ehrlicher, H.-H. Francke, Sybille Oesterlin), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 26: 21)
    - Institut für Höhere Studien und Wissenschaftliche Forschung Wien (S. Sagoroff), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 26: 22)
    - Institut für Politische Jugendbildung Baden Württemberg (Rolf Schlutter), 1965 (Box-folder 26: 23)
    - Institut für Weltwirtschaft an der Universität Kiel (Herbert Giersch, Hans H. Glismann, Kurt Hubner, Karl-Heinz Paque, Horst Rodemer, Klaus-Werner Schatz, Erich Schneider, Anton Zottmann), 1962-1986 (Box-folder 26: 24)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies, Vienna [See Institut für Hohere Studien und Wissenschaftliche Forschung Wien]
    - Institute for Applied Economics (Holmes Brown), 1980 (Box-folder 26: 25)
    - Institute for Economic and Legal Analysis (Patrick M. Boarman), 1976 (Box-folder 26: 26)
    - Institute for Economic Studies (Hideo Aoyama), 1966 (Box-folder 26: 27)
    - Institute for Humane Studies (William W. Beach, John Blundell, James L. Doenges, Walter E. Grinder, Floyd Arthur Harper, William Johnson, Davis E. Keeler, Charles G. Koch, Leonard P. Liggio, William Marina, Lowell B. Mason, George H. Pearson, Louis M. Spadaro, Kenneth S. Templeton, Jr.)
      Includes correspondence with Kurt R. Leube and Laurence S. Moss.
      - 1962-1975 (Box-folder 26: 28)
      - 1976-1986 (Box-folder 27: 1)
    - Institute for Socioeconomic Studies (B. A. Rittersporn, Jr.), 1983 (Box-folder 27: 2)
    - Institute for the Study of Contemporary Social Problems (Sally A. Fichet, Lyman H. Legters), 1978 (Box-folder 27: 3)
    - Institute for Vico Studies (Donald Phillip Verene, Giorgio Tagliacozzo), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 27: 4)
    - Institute of Directors (Jan Hildreth), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 27: 5)
    - Institute of Economic Affairs (Martin J. Anderson, John Burton, John Raybould, Arthur Seldon, Michael J. R. Solly), 1964-1985 (Box-folder 27: 6)
    - Institute of Intercultural Research (Hans A. Fischer-Barnicol), 1977-1987 (Box-folder 27: 7)
    - Institute of Paper Chemistry (A. Neil McLeod), 1961-1965 (Box-folder 27: 8)
    - Institute of Public Affairs (H. N. Warren), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 27: 9)
    - Instituto de Estudios Superiores de la Empresa (Fernando Pereira, Juan J. Toribio), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 27: 10)
    - Instituto Hispanico Austriaco (Heinz Hoedl, Carlos Romero de Leceo), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 27: 11)
    - Instituto Mexicano del Petroleo (Fernando L. Echeagary, Agustin Straffon A.), 1980 (Box-folder 27: 12)
    - Institutum Europaeum (Michael van Notten), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - Intercollegiate Studies Institute (Don Lipsett, John F. Lulves, Jr., E. Victor Milione, Robert Reilly, Robert Ritchie), 1962-1980 (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - International Association of University Presidents (Young Seek Choue), 1977 (Box-folder 28: 3)
    - International Center for Economic Policy Studies (Antony G. A. Fisher, William M. H. Hammett), 1978-1981 (Box-folder 28: 4)
    - International Center for Monetary and Banking Studies (Alexander K. Swoboda), 1975 (Box-folder 28: 5)
    - International Christian University (Holloway Brown, Daishiro Hidaka), 1964 (Box-folder 28: 6)
    - International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences (James A. Baughman, Kasim Gulek, Gerard Radnitzky, Michael Young Warder), 1975-1987 (Box-folder 28: 7)
      Includes clippings and correspondence with and re Sun Myung Moon.
    - International Conference on World Economic Stability (Eugene A. Birnbaum), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 28: 8)
    - International Council for Scientific Development, 1983 (Box-folder 28: 9)
    - International Cultural Foundation [See International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences]
    - International Federation of Institutes for Advanced Study (John A. Clinchy), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 28: 10)
    - International Foundation of Scientists, 1983 (Box-folder 28: 11)
    - International Freedom Academy (Finn Andreen), 1962-1965 (Box-folder 28: 12)
      Includes correspondence with the Institut d'Etudes Politiques (Monika Esterer).
    - International Institute for Economic Research (William R. Allen, Antony G. A. Fisher, Thomas W. Hazlett), 1971-1978 (Box-folder 28: 13)
    - International Labour Review (D. Hobden), 1974 (Box-folder 29: 1)
    - International Media Productions (Heinrich Walter), 1986-1987 (Box-folder 29: 2)
    - International Monetary Fund (Jacques J. Polak), 1976 (Box-folder 29: 3)
    - International Moneyline (Julian M. Snyder), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 29: 4)
    - International Organisation of Private and Independent Doctors (L. A. Crespo), 1984 (Box-folder 29: 5)
    - International Review of Economics and Business (Aldo Montesano), 1983 (Box-folder 29: 6)
    - International Symposium of the Open Society (Nigel Linacre), 1985 (Box-folder 29: 7)
    - International Thrift Institute (M. H. Verrijn Stuart, J. G. Wallis de Vries, H. Wolf), 1962-1964 (Box-folder 29: 8)
    - International University of the Open Society (Gerald Frost), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 29: 9)
    - Investment Seminars Incorporated (Charles E. Githler, III), 1984 (Box-folder 29: 10)
    - Issing, Otmar, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 29: 11)
    - Istituto di Metodologia e Filosofia della Scienza (Angelo Maria Petroni, Riccardo Viale), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 29: 12)
    - Ivens, Michael, 1978 (Box-folder 29: 13)
    - Iwanaga, Shinkichi, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 29: 14)
    - Jackson, Robert H., 1986 (Box-folder 29: 15)
    - Jahoda, Marie, 1978 (Box-folder 29: 16)
    - Japan Broadcasting Corporation (Takeshi Tanaka, Naoya Yoshida), 1980-1985 (Box-folder 29: 17)
    - Japan Broadcast Publishing Company, 1978 (Box-folder 29: 18)
    - Japan Economic Research Institute (Fumio Aoba), 1976 (Box-folder 29: 19)
    - Japan Monkey Centre (M. Kawai), 1966 (Box-folder 29: 20)
    - Japan. Embassy (Germany), 1979 (Box-folder 29: 21)
    - Jaspers, Karl, 1963 (Box-folder 29: 22)
    - Jech, Josef W., 1984 (Box-folder 29: 23)
    - Jenaczek, Friedrich, re Johann Plenge, 1970 (Box-folder 29: 24)
    - Jes Studenteninitiative, 1976 (Box-folder 29: 25)
    - Jescheck, Hans-Heinrich, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 29: 26)
    - Johansson, Mats, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 29: 27)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (James F. Mathias, Henry Allen Moe), 1954-1985 (Box-folder 29: 28)
    - Johns Hopkins University (Milton C. Cummings, Gottfried Dietze, Peter Newman), 1971-1985 (Box-folder 29: 29)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press (Linda S. Powell, Henry Y. K. Tom), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 29: 30)
    - Johnsen, Hans Chr. Garmann, 1982 (Box-folder 29: 31)
    - Johnson, Christopher, 1985 (Box-folder 29: 32)
    - Johnson, D. Gale, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 29: 33)
    - Johnson, Daniel, 1983 (Box-folder 29: 34)
    - Johnson, Elizabeth, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 29: 35)
    - Johnson, Harry G., 1970-1976 (Box-folder 29: 36)
    - Johnson, Paul, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 29: 37)
    - Johnston, William M., 1984 (Box-folder 29: 38)
    - Johr, W. A., 1980 (Box-folder 29: 39)
    - Jojima, Kunihiro, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 29: 40)
    - Jones-Lee, M. W., 1983 (Box-folder 29: 41)
    - Jong, Professor de, 1977 (Box-folder 29: 42)
    - Joseph, Lord Keith, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 29: 43)
    - Journal of Austrian Economics (Walter Block, Roger W. Garrison), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 29: 44)
    - Journal of Law and Economics (Ronald H. Coase), 1977 (Box-folder 29: 45)
    - Journal of Libertarian Studies (Murray N. Rothbard), 1978 (Box-folder 29: 46)
    - Judis, John B., 1984 (Box-folder 29: 47)
    - Jung, Richard, 1963-1979 (Box-folder 29: 48)
    - Junge Union Deutschlands (Christoph Bohr), 1985 (Box-folder 29: 49)
    - Justus Liebig-Universität Giessen (Herr Alewell, Armin Bohnet, Hans G. Monissen), 1980-1983 (Box-folder 29: 50)
    - Kahn, R. F., 1931 (Box-folder 29: 51)
    - Kaiser, Joseph H., 1966-1982 (Box-folder 29: 52)
    - Kaldor, Nicholas, 1981 (Box-folder 29: 53)
    - Kasai, Jiuji G., 1964 (Box-folder 30: 1)
    - Kaser, Max and Erna, 1976 (Box-folder 30: 2)
    - Kast R., Migue, 1980 (Box-folder 30: 3)
    - Kastler, Alfred, re mainly the manifesto on world hunger of 1981 June 24 signed by more than 50 Nobel laureates, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 30: 4)
      Includes clippings and correspondence with the Groupe de Bruxelles Satyagraha (Jean Fabre and Giovanni Negri) and Rosalyn S. Yalow.
    - Katz, Bernard, 1984 (Box-folder 30: 5)
    - Kauder, Emil, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 30: 6)
    - Kawakami, Genechi, 1981 (Box-folder 30: 7)
    - Keidel, Dr., 1962-1981 (Box-folder 30: 8)
    - Keizai Doyukai (Seiichi Yamashita), 1964 (Box-folder 30: 9)
    - Keller, Rudi, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 30: 10)
    - Kellner, Anton, 1962 (Box-folder 30: 11)
    - Kemp, Arthur and Helene, 1963-1986 (Box-folder 30: 12)
    - Kemp, Jack, 1979 (Box-folder 30: 13)
    - Kendal and Dent Ltd. (Joco Perestrello), 1977 (Box-folder 30: 14)
    - Kendall, Raymond, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 30: 15)
    - Kennan, George F., 1984 (Box-folder 30: 16)
    - Kevelson, Roberta, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 30: 17)
    - Kewenig, Wilhelm A., 1984 (Box-folder 30: 18)
    - Keynes, Lord John Maynard, 1927-1946 (Box-folder 30: 19)
    - Keynes Seminar (D. Crabtree), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 30: 20)
    - Kiesch, Guy, 1981 (Box-folder 30: 21)
    - Kikawada, Kazutaka, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 30: 22)
    - Kim, Ip-Sam, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 30: 23)
    - Kindermann, Gottfried-Karl, 1964-1976 (Box-folder 30: 24)
    - Kingston, William, 1981 (Box-folder 30: 25)
    - Kirkbride, John M., 1980-1982 (Box-folder 30: 26)
    - Kirzner, Israel M., 1963-1985 (Box-folder 30: 27)
      Includes correspondence with Richard A. Cornell, Richard H. Fink, Sanford Ikeda (Austrian Economics Newsletter), and John Kunze.
    - Kitch, Edmund W., 1983 (Box-folder 30: 28)
    - Kitching, Ron, 1976 (Box-folder 30: 29)
    - Kiuchi, Nobutane, 1962-1981 (Box-folder 30: 30)
    - Klaus, Josef, 1967 (Box-folder 30: 31)
    - Klein, Benjamin, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 30: 32)
    - Klein, Kurt, 1963 (Box-folder 30: 33)
    - Kleinewefers, Henner, 1983 (Box-folder 30: 34)
    - Kliemt, Hartmut, 1980 (Box-folder 30: 35)
    - Klockau, Walter J., Jr., 1962-1981 (Box-folder 30: 36)
    - Klose, Dr., 1974 (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - Kloten, Norbert, 1984 (Box-folder 31: 2)
    - Klotz, J., 1956 (Box-folder 31: 3)
    - Kluver, Heinrich, 1954-1976, 1978 (Box-folder 31: 4)
      Includes correspondence with Harriet E. Schwenk.
    - Kment, Alfred and Annamaria, 1981 (Box-folder 31: 5)
    - Knapp, Horst, 1964 (Box-folder 31: 6)
    - Knox, A. David, 1984 (Box-folder 31: 7)
    - Knutel, Rolf, 1984 (Box-folder 31: 8)
    - Kobayashi, Hiroshi, 1979 (Box-folder 31: 9)
    - Koch, Michael, 1983 (Box-folder 31: 10)